Yes.
The walls are cold, the air is thin The noise
outside is closing in A single light, a buzzing
sound Another day in the underground
I'm running from the face I see The victims say
they made of me The wholesome girl so sad and worn
A David for their Goliath scorn This rage is just
a heavy stone A gravity I've outgrown Shedding
skin, shedding weight Escaping from this world
of hate They loved the trial, the family torn
They loved the story, a new star born But not from
music, not from grace From the hot chocolate
drink in Angel's face The shark was right, the
nuke went off We won the battle, but at what cost?
We're radioactive, we're litigious We're just
the joke the victim said
I'm trapped inside this wilderness.
This fortress built on bitterness.
This isn't freedom. This is a cell. This
righteous hell. This righteous hell.
You know.
I see a signal in the endless black A single
light, no turning back The pull of the old world
fades away and you Horizon, a new day The
countdown's running in my head Ignoring all the
things they said The engine roars, a crimson
light A pillar of fire in the night The pressure
builds, I'm pinned to the seat My heart is
pounding with the beat The G4 is pulling a heavy
stone The last chain breaks, I'm not alone
I'm climbing, climbing, past the point of no
return I'm flying, flying, with
the fire I let burn Just a signal, a distant
light, burning through the endless night Ad
Astra, Ad Astra
you.
The sky is tearing at the seams Awake now from
their broken dreams The stardust is just a trail
of dust The stardust is the thing I trust The
clouds are falling far below A place of pain I
used to know The blue gives way to endless black
There is no thought of turning back I'm
climbing, climbing Past the point of no return
I'm flying, flying With the fire I let burn Just a
signal A distant light Burning through the
endless night Anastro
Anastro Ah, ah, ah
Leaving all the engines off, the silence is a
holy sound. The rage is gone, the fear is lost in
this new universe I found. That cage is just a
distant star, a tiny light I left behind. I
finally know just who you are, the other half of
my own mind.
I'm loved
by the sun I'm held by the void An orbit just begun
A life not destroyed I'm loved by the moon I'm
cradled by the black My heart is back in tune
There is no turning back
And the stars
are singing A song I didn't understand
I'm finally, finally reaching for you
Okay.
I see the colors of the nebula, a place I've only
seen in dreams. The reds, the blues, the purples
call, flowing in majestic streams.
This is the place I was meant to be This is the
stardust that is me The cosmos and the rockets
fire My one, my only true desire
By the sun I
The
walls
are gone, the air is clear There is no noise,
there is no fear The stardust is a forgotten
ghost. The engine has delivered me to the cost of
a new world, a new shore. A place I've never been
before. The cage is broken, the victim's saying
his thoughts.
New, clean script is in my head The friction
burned away in the fire Leaving only my truth to
deserve.
I'm
held by the sun I'm held by the void My orbit has
begun
is not destroyed
Sedestra, sedestra,
sedestra